[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "If they had gone behind Congress' back as you claimed, do you think you can get this overturned legally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Probably not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States of America"]}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Yes, I think that to assume that the United States of America would use a drone and a hellfire missile to attack someone sitting in a cafe -- look, this goes back to our previous conversation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Do you have any message for Newt Gingrich?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Oh, listen, Newt and I have been friends for many, many years.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Newt Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "I think maybe we need a congressional hearing on the whole issue of what is a danger to the entire flight and what we should -- I think we need to call witnesses since they have made this policy change.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "I'm great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "This looks a fun gig, the movie.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Is he feeling the heat now, you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "I'm sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Were Amy Poehler and Tina Fey a little unfair to her, did you think, at the Golden Globes with their jibe about her young boyfriends?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "You know, I have to say that we have to get a little less sensitive, you know, with the comedians.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amy Poehler", "Tina Fey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "That's the point you're making, is everyone getting a little thin-skinned here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "I think we really are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "Is it an important thing to have, you think, to affirm to the world that women matter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "I think absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "What is your view about women working from home, in particular, women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Well, I think it's really hard to work from home.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "Tell me about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "I started to, but it didn't really work out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "He directs this movie, doesn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Yes, he's the director of the movie and, you know, he is sharing in all of the responsibilities and, in fact, takes on most of the responsibilities where men have such a difficult time being the man behind the woman, he's actually such a great example of someone who is comfortable in that position and you know fills the slots where he has to so that I can go off and do my work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "So you know what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Get out of here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "When you look back and when you finished it, what did you think about the career you've had?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "You know, in doing it -- and you feel it -- the impact didn't, you know, work on me, there's no question about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "It's about the love of music for you, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "You know, it was totally by luck that I had gotten into music.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Am I wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "No, you're not wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "And have you been surprised by them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "AVIS: I've not been surprised, honestly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Would you like to get married to a man one day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "I've been married twice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "But are you -- are you pleased to see the way the gay marriage debate has gone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Oh, I'm very pleased.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kelly"]}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "``", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "CC", "``", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "What did you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Look, well, as far as Kelly is concerned -- and I've been talking about that -- we had a different judgment as to how she reacted to two songs that I gave her that become huge hits, \"Since You've Been Gone,\" and \"Behind These Hazel Eyes,\" as well, you know, as \"Break Away\" and others.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Have you spoken to her since?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "This is a dispute.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Simon & Garfunkel"]}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "What would the single be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "\"Bridge Over Troubled Water\" with Simon & Garfunkel.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "And, finally, which artist would you take?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "(INAUDIBLE).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alicia Keys"]}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "If you could have one to sing to you for the rest of your life, just you and them on a desert island?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "TO", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Well, let me -- I would point to Alicia Keys, who, with Pager Edge (ph), I discovered, a Renaissance young woman who writes her own materials, stunning to look at, a major talent within the industry.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "And how would you change it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Well, I -- yes, you're right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Have you seen the movie \"Zero Dark Thirty\" yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "No, I haven't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "From what you have heard of it, what is -- what is your opinion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "What I have heard about it, it's a good movie, all right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "What is the quickest and best way to fix that international relationship between Pakistan and the United States?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "CC", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "I feel, yes, they have never been that bad, and I think in my time, the relations were good, although we were facing the same threat, and we were dealing with the threat in our own ways.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pakistan", "United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "What is your view of the use of drones generally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "Well, use of drones, there are two uses of drones.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "NIDENTIFIED FEMALE: Do you want to take any of the babies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "Isn't that beautiful?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]